myurldab.com 2016-12-01

# Privacy Policy

## Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

  *     * ### Analytics

      * ### Google Analytics

Personal Data: Cookie and Usage Data

    * ### Contacting the User

      * ### Contact form

Personal Data: Email, First Name and Last Name

    * ### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

      * ### Twitter Tweet button and social widgets

Personal Data: Cookie and Usage Data

## UrlDab and Owner

## Types of Data collected

Among the types of Personal Data that UrlDab collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookie, Usage Data, First Name, Last Name and Email. 

Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection.  
The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using UrlDab.  
Any use of Cookies - or of other tracking tools - by the Application or by the owners of third party services used by UrlDab, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.  
Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for UrlDab to provide its services.

The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through UrlDab and declares to have the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the UrlDab of all responsibility.

## Mode and place of processing the Data

### Method of processing

The UrlDab processes the Data of Users in proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
Access to the Data may be available to Data Processors such as employees involved with the processing or to external parties providing services to the UrlDab, third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communication agencies. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the UrlDab at any time.

### Place

The Data is processed at the UrlDab headquarters, unless stated otherwise in the rest of this document.

### Conservation Time

The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request the UrlDab for their suspension or removal.

## The use of the collected Data

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Application to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Analytics, Interaction with external social networks and platforms and Contacting the User. 

The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document.

## Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

### Analytics

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

#### Google Analytics (Google)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of UrlDab, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. 

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. 

Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

### Contacting the User

#### Contact form (UrlDab)

By filling in the contact form with their Data, the Users authorizes UrlDab to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.

Personal Data collected: Email, First Name and Last Name. 

### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

These services allow interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of UrlDab.  
The interaction and information obtained by UrlDab are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.  
If a service enabling interaction with social networks is installed it may still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it. 

#### Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter)

The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. 

Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy](http://twitter.com/privacy)

## Additional information about Data collection and processing

### Legal Action

The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the UrlDab, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of UrlDab or the related services. 

### Additional Information about User's Personal Data

In addition to the information in this privacy policy, UrlDab may provide the User with contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data. 

### System Logs and Maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, UrlDab and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with UrlDab (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address). 

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the UrlDab at any time at its contact information. 

### The rights of Users

Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the UrlDab to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the UrlDab at the contact information set out above. 

### Changes to this privacy policy

The UrlDab reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using UrlDab and can request the UrlDab to erase the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the UrlDab has about Users. 

### Definitions and legal references 

#### Personal Data (or Data)

Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.

#### Usage Data

Information collected automatically from UrlDab (or third party services employed in UrlDab ), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use UrlDab, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment.

#### User

The individual using UrlDab, which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refer.

#### Data Subject

The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers to.

#### Data Processor

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization authorized by the UrlDab to process the Personal Data in compliance with this privacy policy.

#### UrlDab (or Application Owner, or Owner)

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another UrlDab, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of UrlDab. The UrlDab, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of UrlDab.

#### UrlDab

The hardware or software tool by which the User Personal Data is collected.

#### Cookie

Small piece of data stored in the User's device.

* * *

#### Legal information

Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies.

This privacy policy is solely about UrlDab.
